Michael Caine invites you to celebrate the '60s:
The decade that changed the world
My Generation is a documentary, music, history film directed by David Batty.
The vivid and inspiring story of British film icon Michael Caine's
personal journey through 1960s swinging London.
Self, played by Michael Caine.
Self (voice), played by David Bailey.
Self (voice), played by Twiggy.
Self (voice), played by Mary Quant.
Self (voice), played by Marianne Faithfull.
Self (voice), played by Joan Collins.
My Generation is a 2017 documentary film directed by
David Batty and presented by Michael Caine.
It follows the cultural revolution that occurred in 1960s England and interviews various icons and key figures
such as David Bailey, Roger Daltrey, Marianne Faithfull, Paul McCartney, Mary Quant and Twiggy.
The film contains an abundance of archive footage and its soundtrack
contains the 1965 song of the same name by The Who.
The film explores themes of london, england,
swinging 60s, 1960s, swinging london.
The tone is uplifting.